ozspeedtest.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Oz Broadband Speed Test

### 11th February 2008

We understand that your privacy is important. As a result we feel it is in our best interests to be forward with users about what information we collect about you, and what we do with this information. We hope this makes you more comfortable in using our site.

### Personal Information

  * We only collect personal information when you register at our site.
  * We only use cookies to store your personal preferences.
  * Our servers automatically record information about your visit, such as your IP address, the pages you view, your web browser, and the time and date of your visit.

### Information Use

  * We may use personal your information to improve the content on our site.
  * We use your personal information to customise the content and/or layout of each page.
  * Your personal information is not shared with anyone except where a law enforcement agency, or other government agency, exercises its legal authority to require access to the information.
  * We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

### Site Ads

We try and bring you advertisements that are of interest to you. We have a relationship with [Google](http://www.google.com/) that allows us to place ads on our site. As a result of your visit to our site, Google may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information please consult Google's [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

### Further Information

For further information, or if you feel that we are not following our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at any time.
